Guide to the George W. Wilbur Family Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Personal Correspondence, 1807-1954; Series I; 12.25; (31 boxes)
  - WILBUR, SARAH ANN COOK
    - Correspondence with Others
      - Correspondence, 1884 (Box 24, Folder 523)
      - Correspondence, 1885 (Box 24, Folder 524-525)
      - Correspondence, 1886 (Box 24, Folder 526)
      - Correspondence, 1887 (Box 24, Folder 527)
      - Correspondence, 1888 (Box 24, Folder 528-529)
      - Correspondence, 1889 (Box 24, Folder 530)
      - Correspondence, 1890 (Box 24, Folder 531)
      - Correspondence, 1891-93 (Box 24, Folder 532)
      - Correspondence, 1895-96 (Box 24, Folder 533)
      - Correspondence, 1897 (Box 24, Folder 534)
      - Correspondence, 1898 (Box 24, Folder 535)
      - Correspondence, 1899 (Box 24, Folder 536-537)
        See also: Letter of 1899 Oct 2 in Box 10, folder 211
      - Correspondence, 1900 (Box 24, Folder 538-539)
      - Correspondence, 1901 (Box 24, Folder 540-541)
      - Correspondence, 1902 (Box 25, Folder 542-543)
      - Correspondence, 1903 (Box 25, Folder 544-545)
      - Correspondence, 1904 (Box 25, Folder 546)
      - Correspondence (Box 25, Folder 547-548)
    - Invitations
      - Invitations, 1878-86 (Box 25, Folder 549)
      - Invitations, 1887-89 (Box 25, Folder 550)
      - Invitations, 1891-1902 (Box 25, Folder 551)
  - JONES, SUSAN WILBUR
    - For Susan Wilbur Jones' other correspondence, see: folders 341-369, 488-493
    - Correspondence with Ellen Rice Wilbur
      - For Ellen Rice Wilbur's other correspondence, see: folders 324-340, 475-476, 566c-580
      - Correspondence, 1900-18 (Box 25, Folder 552)
    - Correspondence with Susan W. Rice
      For Susan W. Rice's other correspondence, see: folders 373-374, 494, 567, 582-585a
      - Correspondence, 1902-12 (Box 25, Folder 553)
    - Correspondence with Llewellyn Jones
      - Correspondence, [1916-29], n.d. (Box 25, Folder 553a)
    - Correspondence with E. P. Warren
      - Correspondence, 1907-27, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 553b)
    - Correspondence with "Mary"
      - Correspondence, [1918-27] (Box 25, Folder 553c)
      - Correspondence, [1928] (Box 25, Folder 553d-e)
    - Correspondence with Others
      - Correspondence, 1898-1901 (Box 25, Folder 554)
      - Correspondence, 1902-07 (Box 25, Folder 555)
      - Correspondence, 1908-09 (Box 25a, Folder 556)
      - Correspondence, 1911-13 (Box 25a, Folder 557)
      - Correspondence, 1914 (Box 25a, Folder 558-559)
      - Correspondence, [1915]-17 (Box 25a, Folder 560)
      - Correspondence, 1918-38 (Box 25a, Folder 560a)
      - Correspondence, 1946-54 (Box 25a, Folder 561)
      - Correspondence (Box 25a, Folder 562)
    - Invitations and Christmas Cards
      - Invitations, 1898-1915 (Box 26, Folder 563)
        See also: folders 404-420
      - Invitations, 1916-51 (Box 26, Folder 564)
      - Invitations, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 565)
      - Christmas cards, [1916] (Box 26, Folder 566)
      - Christmas cards, [1930-46] (Box 26, Folder 566a)
      - Christmas cards, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 566b)
  - WILBUR, ELLEN RICE
    - For Ellen Rice Wilbur's other correspondence, see: folders 324-339, 475-574, 552
    - Correspondence with Albert H. Wilbur
      For Albert H. Wilbur's other correspondence, see: folders 252-323, 421-474, 581
      - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 26, Folder 566c)
    - Correspondence with Susan W. Rice
      - For Susan W. Rice's other correspondence, see: folders 373-374, 494, 553, 582-585a
      - Correspondence, 1886-1927, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 567)
    - Correspondence with Cornelia Warren
      - Correspondence, 1910-17 (Box 26, Folder 567a)
      - Correspondence, 1918-20 (Box 26, Folder 567b)
    - Correspondence with Others
      - Correspondence, 1861-72 (Box 26, Folder 568)
      - Correspondence, 1873-75 (Box 26, Folder 569)
      - Correspondence, 1876-81 (Box 26, Folder 570)
      - Correspondence, 1884-87 (Box 26, Folder 571)
      - Correspondence, 1889-99 (Box 26, Folder 572)
      - Correspondence, 1909 (Box 26, Folder 573)
      - Correspondence, 1916-27 (Box 26, Folder 574)
      - Correspondence, 1928 (Box 26, Folder 575)
      - Correspondence, 1930-37 (Box 26, Folder 575a)
      - Correspondence (Box 26a, Folder 576-577)
    - Invitations and Greeting Cards
      - Condolence cards from Susan W. Rice's funeral, [1928] (Box 26a, Folder 578)
      - Invitations, 1914-31, n.d. (Box 26a, Folder 579)
        See also: Boxes 19 and 20, folders 404-419
      - Christmas cards, 1930, n.d. (Box 26a, Folder 580)
        See also: Box 20, folder 420
  - WILBUR, ALBERT H.
    - For Albert H. Wilbur's other correspondence, see: folders 252-323, 421-474, 566c
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence
      - Correspondence, 1865-1900, n.d. (Box 26a, Folder 581)
  - RICE, SUSAN W.
    - For Susan W. Rice's other correspondence, see: folders 373-374, 494, 553, 567
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence
      - Correspondence incoming, 1864-1916, n.d. (Box 26a, Folder 582)
      - Invitations, 1907-13 (Box 27, Folder 583)
        See also: Folders 413-419
      - Invitations, 1915 (Box 27, Folder 584)
      - Invitations, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 585)
      - Christmas card, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 585a)
  - OTHER PERSONAL CORRESPONDENCE
    - Correspondence, 1807, 1817 (Box 27, Folder 586)
    - Correspondence, 1852-59 (Box 27, Folder 587)
    - Correspondence, 1861 (Box 27, Folder 588)
    - Correspondence, 1867-76 (Box 27, Folder 589)
    - Correspondence, 1877-82 (Box 27, Folder 590)
      See also: Letters of [1879] Jul 25 and 29 in Box 23, folder 512
    - Correspondence, 1883-99 (Box 27, Folder 591)
    - Correspondence, 1900-32 (Box 27, Folder 592)
    - Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 593-594)
    - Unaddressed invitations, 1871-1909 (Box 27, Folder 595)
    - Unaddressed invitations, 1913-20, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 595a)
    - Christmas cards, 1903-28 (Box 27, Folder 596)
    - Christmas cards, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 597)
- George W. Wilbur's Professional Papers, 1855-1931; Series II; 20.4; (50 boxes)
  Series II, George W. Wilbur's Professional Papers, is organized into twelve subseries, Cases: Contract Files, Cases: Long Term Individual Client Files, Cases: Mining Company Files, Cases: Probate Files, Cases: Real Estate Files, Cases: Street Improvements Files, Cases: Other Case Files, Cases: Fragments from Files, Professional Correspondence, Financial Papers, Notebooks, and Printed Material. The Case files are arranged alphabetically by case name within each section. With the exception of the Long Term Individual Client and Mining Company sections, which have been arranged chronologically, the material in the folders has been left in the order received.
  - CASES: CONTRACT FILES
    - Almini Company vs. Charles Seats, 1906 (Box 28, Folder 598)
    - Almini Company vs. Mary Logan Tucker, 1904-06 (Box 28, Folder 599)
    - Art Novelty Manufacturing Co. vs. Union Wholesale Liquor Company, 1920-21 (Box 28, Folder 600)
    - Beatty, Arthur vs. Adrian C. Hyatt, 1926-29 (Box 28, Folder 601)
      See also: E. Hartwell vs. Adrian C. Hyatt, Box 28, folder 612
    - Belowsky, J. vs. Stanley Kendresik, 1924 (Box 28, Folder 602)
    - Block, Sara L. vs. Leona B. Hutchinson, 1925-26 (Box 28, Folder 603)
    - Christopherson, G.A. vs. George R. Stewart and J. Schneider, 1930-31 (Box 28, Folder 604-605)
    - Downey, Sarah et al. vs. Gertrude Coleman, 1922 (Box 28, Folder 606)
    - Felton, Mathias vs. John Schneider, 1930 (Box 28, Folder 607)
    - Field, Judson L. vs. Harry W. Finney, 1921 (Box 28, Folder 608)
    - Foote, D. E., 1872-77 (Box 28, Folder 609)
    - Fuller, Alonzo M. vs. Webb S. Edwards, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 610)
      See also: Alonzo M. Fuller vs. Charles T. Luckow and The Globe Laundry Co. filed below under Other Cases, Box 63, folders 1183-1186
    - Gara, Ella Snell vs. A. R. Eck, 1927-28 (Box 28, Folder 611)
    - Hartwell, E. vs. Adrian C. Hyatt, 1927 (Box 28, Folder 612)
      See also: Arthur Beatty vs. Adrian C. Hyatt, Box 28, folder 601
    - Holland, Harry L. vs. County of Cook, 1908 (Box 28, Folder 613-615)
    - Ideal Printing Press Repair Shop, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 616)
    - Jaicks, Andrew Jr. et al. vs. A. Dalgard, 1927-28 (Box 28, Folder 617-618)
    - Jones, Joseph F. vs. Joseph D. Tuthill, 1884-85 (Box 28, Folder 619)
    - Kanara, Edward et al. vs. Benjamin C. Pittsford, 1931 (Box 28, Folder 620)
    - Klump, Cyrus C. vs. H. E. Redding, 1925 (Box 28, Folder 621)
    - Kramp, William vs. Harry M. Lubliner, 1929 (Box 28, Folder 622)
    - Lowery, Ralph vs. Penn Carolan and Wesley Trebass, 1919-20 (Box 28, Folder 623)
    - Melville, Americus B. vs. Charles H. Woodward, 1925-28 (Box 29, Folder 624-631)
      See also: Americus B. Melville in Other Cases, Box 64, folder 1214
    - Mortgage Investment Trust, 1928-29 (Box 29, Folder 632)
    - Murphy Brothers Teaming Co. vs. Van Sickle-Wertz Co., 1928-29 (Box 29, Folder 633)
    - National Surface Guard Co. vs. Whitehouse Stone Company, 1918-19 (Box 29, Folder 634-636)
    - Newburn, Charlotte E. vs. Mary Wiggins, 1917 (Box 29, Folder 637)
    - Nikoli, Todor vs. John Nimick, et al., 1929 (Box 29, Folder 638-642)
    - Paulson, L. P. vs. Williams-Wendt Co., 1923 (Box 30, Folder 643)
    - Percy, Louise W. vs. John B. Orlando, 1924 (Box 30, Folder 644)
    - Postman, John vs. Dr. Hiram J. Smith, 1930 (Box 30, Folder 645)
    - Revere Clock Company vs. Geo. R. Stewart Company, 1929-30 (Box 30, Folder 646)
    - Settles, Sylvia vs. Milan H. and Olive Hulbert, 1920 (Box 30, Folder 647)
    - Sevin, Morris vs. Robert A. Elliott, 1927 (Box 30, Folder 648)
    - Stewart, George R. vs. William E. Dodson, 1916 (Box 30, Folder 649)
    - Streeter-Amet Weighing & Recording Company vs. Columbus, Sandusky & Hocking Railroad Company, 1899-1900 (Box 30, Folder 650)
    - Tiberi, John vs. Fannie Schut, 1928-31 (Box 30, Folder 651-652)
    - Warder, John B. vs. Irving C. Osten-Sacken, 1922 (Box 30, Folder 653)
    - Wendell, Anna B., 1920 (Box 30, Folder 654)
    - Whitworth, Mary W. et al. vs. Jonathan Heywood, 1878-79 (Box 30, Folder 655)
    - Woodsmall, F. M. vs. S. Nelson, 1906 (Box 30, Folder 656)
  - CASES: LONG TERM INDIVIDUAL CLIENT FILES
    - Burke, Michael and Robert L.
      - City of Chicago vs. M. Burke and R. G. Neiss, 1909-10 (Box 31, Folder 657)
      - Guy, Harry vs. Michael Burke, et al., 1909-11 (Box 31, Folder 658-663)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, research notes, clippings, documents, 1917-18 (Box 31, Folder 664)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, research notes, clippings, documents, 1919 (Box 31, Folder 665-666)
      - Court-martial of Robert L. Burke, 1918 (Box 31, Folder 667)
      - Court-martial of Robert L. Burke, 1919 (Box 31, Folder 668-670)
      - Burke, Robert L. vs. Julian Berliner, 1917-19 (Box 31, Folder 671)
      - Will of Michael Burke, 1919 (Box 31, Folder 672)
      - Miscellaneous bills, receipts, and correspondence, 1920 (Box 32, Folder 673-681)
      - Branson, Pearl M. vs. Robert L. Burke, 1921 (Box 32, Folder 682)
      - Correspondence, clippings, 1921 (Box 32, Folder 683-689)
      - Correspondence, 1922 (Box 33, Folder 690)
      - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 33, Folder 691)
      - Correspondence and documents, 1924 (Box 33, Folder 692)
      - Correspondence, 1925 (Box 33, Folder 693)
      - Official Map, North half of the City of Miami Beach, Florida, 1925
        See: Oversize, folder 1880
      - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 33, Folder 694)
      - Lanning, Eliza B. vs. Robert L. Burke, 1925-26 (Box 33, Folder 695)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence and documents, 1927 (Box 33, Folder 696-700)
      - Correspondence, 1928-29 (Box 33, Folder 701)
      - Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 702)
    - Hulbert, Thomas H.
      - Accounts, 1900-02 (Box 33, Folder 703)
      - Reddington, John F. vs. National Engine Company, et al., 1910-18 (Box 33, Folder 704-708)
        With countersuit filed by Thomas H. Hulbert against the National Engine Company
      - Weber, Beth vs. Thomas H. Hulbert, 1919-22 (Box 34, Folder 709-712)
      - Village of Oak Park vs. Thomas H. Hulbert, 1920-23 (Box 34, Folder 713-717)
      - City of Chicago vs. Thomas H. Hulbert, 1927-28 (Box 34, Folder 718-721)
      - Vogel, Clara, estate of, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 722)
      - Miscellaneous, 1904-30 (Box 35, Folder 723-730)
    - Jones, Roswell N.
      - Hansen, Christ et al. vs. Central Casualty Underwriters, 1922-25 (Box 35, Folder 731)
      - Jones, Roswell N. vs. William Robert and Emily M. Gilchrist, Chicago Title and Trust Company, Samuel Berenbaum and F. A. Rauch, 1923-24 (Box 35, Folder 732-735)
      - Goodrich, Morris vs. Lincoln Robey Building, 1926-30 (Box 36, Folder 736-739)
        Roswell Jones was an intervening petitioner in this case
      - Jones, Roswell N. vs. William I. and Mary Madeline Gillen, Chicago Title and Trust Company, et al., 1926-29 (Box 36, Folder 740)
      - Jones, Roswell N. vs. Alfred A. and Anna Behnke, 1927-28 (Box 36, Folder 741-742)
      - Jones, Roswell N. vs. Frank J. and May A. Schmidt, 1927-28 (Box 36, Folder 743-744)
      - Merchants and Manufacturers Securities Company vs. George W. Ford, Marie S. Ford, Roswell N. Jones, Daisy I. Jones, et al., 1927-29 (Box 36, Folder 745-748)
      - Jones, Roswell N. vs. Frederick and Minnie E. Coleman, 1929 (Box 36, Folder 749)
    - Rice, Charlotte and Francis H.
      - See also: Francis H. and George H. Rice in series IV, Box 95, folders 1643-1674
      - Miscellaneous deeds and letters, 1855-85 (Box 37, Folder 750-751)
      - Ohio tax receipts of Charlotte Rice, 1877-87 (Box 37, Folder 752)
      - Ingalls, Nancy H. vs. Charlotte and Francis H. Rice, 1886-92 (Box 37, Folder 753-756)
      - Hovey, William F., administrator of the estate of Nancy Ingalls vs. Charlotte and Francis H. Rice, 1893, 1895 (Box 37, Folder 757)
      - Rice, Charlotte and Francis H. vs. Nancy H. Ingalls, revived in the name of Homer H. Wright, 1896-97 (Box 37, Folder 758-761)
      - Emerson, Waty B. vs. Estate of Francis H. Rice, 1899-1900 (Box 37, Folder 762)
      - Ingalls, Nancy H. vs. Charlotte and Francis H. Rice (Box 38, Folder 763-770)
  - CASES: MINING COMPANY FILES
    - Glick & Ingham vs. Pittsburgh Concentrating & Mining
      Full heading: Morris Glick and Joseph
      - Ingham vs. Pittsburgh Concentrating and Mining Company
      - Documents and correspondence, 1891-93 (Box 38, Folder 771-772)
      - Documents and correspondence, 1894 (Box 38, Folder 773-775)
      - Correspondence and bills, 1895-96 (Box 39, Folder 776)
      - Correspondence, 1897 (Box 39, Folder 777)
      - Correspondence, 1898-99 (Box 39, Folder 778)
      - Documents, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 779)
      - In the Court of Appeals, State of Colorado. Morris Glick and Joseph Ingham, Appellees, vs. The Pittsburg Concentrating and Mining Company, Appellant. Brief and Argument of Appellant. (Box 39, Folder 780)
      - In the Court of Appeals, State of Colorado. Morris Glick and Joseph Ingham, Appellees, vs. The Pittsburg Concentrating and Mining Company, Appellant. Reply of Appellant to Brief and Argument of Appellees. (Box 39, Folder 781)
      - In the Court of Appeals, State of Colorado. Morris Glick and Joseph Ingham, Appellees, vs. The Pittsburg Concentrating and Mining Company, Appellant. Abstract of Record and Assignment of Errors. (Box 39, Folder 782)
    - Ruby Chief Mining and Milling Company
      - Documents, correspondence, receipts, 1885 (Box 39, Folder 783-784)
        See also: Oversize, Box 112, folder 1846
      - Documents, correspondence, receipts, 1886 (Box 39, Folder 785-786)
      - Documents, correspondence, accounts, 1887-89 (Box 39, Folder 787)
        See also: Oversize, Box 112, folder 1847
      - Documents, correspondence, 1893 (Box 39, Folder 788)
      - Pocket notebook of research notes on cases, 1893 (Box 39, Folder 789)
        Diary of business trip to Colorado in back
      - Documents, correspondence (Box 39, Folder 790)
        See also: Oversize, box 112, folder 1848
      - Plat of Mines of Ruby Chief Mining and Milling Company
        See: Oversize, folder 1879a
      - Gurley, Charles D. vs. Ruby Chief Mining and Milling Company, 1887 (Box 39, Folder 791)
        See also: Oversize, box 112, folder 1850
      - Gurley, Charles D. vs. Ruby Chief Mining and Milling Company, 1888 (Box 39, Folder 792)
      - Gurley, Charles D. vs. Ruby Chief Mining and Milling Company, 1893 (Box 40, Folder 793-794)
      - Gurley, Charles D. vs. Ruby Chief Mining and Milling Company (Box 40, Folder 795)
      - In the Appellate Court of Illinois. First District. October Term, A.D. 1889. Howard F. Smith, Appellant, vs. Moses A. Hawkes, et al., Appellees. Brief and Argument for Appellees [and] Brief and Argument for Appellant [and] Reply Brief and Argument for Appellant [and] Abstract of Record. (Box 40, Folder 796)
      - Hawkes, Louise R. vs. Joel V. Taylor and the Ruby Chief Mining and Milling Company, 1893-97 (Box 40, Folder 797)
      - Prentice, L. P. vs. Ruby Chief Mining and Milling Company, 1893-97 (Box 40, Folder 798)
      - Metzler, S. S. and V. E. Metzler vs. Ruby Chief Mining and Milling Company, 1897 (Box 40, Folder 799)
  - CASES: PROBATE FILES
    - Brown, Harry V., 1925-26 (Box 41, Folder 800-803)
    - Clougher, Elfrieda G. and George D., 1922-30 (Box 41, Folder 804-807)
    - Collier, George, 1923 (Box 41, Folder 808)
    - Considine, Catherine and Michael J., 1905-22 (Box 41, Folder 809-814)
      See also: Mary E. Harney, Box 43, folders 829-838
    - Doyle, Emma A., 1923-25 (Box 42, Folder 815-816)
      See also: Emma A. Doyle under Real Estate, Box 48, folder 905
    - Fankhauser, Ray, 1910-24 (Box 42, Folder 817-822)
    - Field, Elizabeth P., 1926-28 (Box 42, Folder 823-826)
    - Fitzgerald, Mary, 1914-17 (Box 42, Folder 827-828)
    - Harney, Mary E., 1921-25 (Box 43, Folder 829-838)
      See also: Catherine and Michael J. Considine, Box 41, folders 829-838
    - Hecketsweiler, Louisa S., 1923-26 (Box 43, Folder 839-840)
    - Mossop, Emily Jane, 1931 (Box 44, Folder 841)
      Aunt of Llewellyn Jones
    - O'Shea, Nellie, 1929-30 (Box 44, Folder 842)
    - Robbel, Louise M., 1921-24 (Box 44, Folder 843-846)
    - Scoville, Jane, 1925 (Box 44, Folder 847)
    - Smith, Maria, 1899-1930 (Box 44, Folder 848-849)
    - Springer, Warren, 1911-15 (Box 44, Folder 850-857)
    - Thompson, William H., 1921-23 (Box 44, Folder 858-859)
    - Warren, Agnes C., 1921-25 (Box 45, Folder 860-863)
    - Warren, Samuel T., 1924-26 (Box 45, Folder 864-865)
    - Weaver, Agnes, 1914-25 (Box 46, Folder 866-880)
    - Wisniewski, Antonina, 1925-26 (Box 46, Folder 881)
  - CASES: REAL ESTATE FILES
    - Atwood, David F., 1925 (Box 47, Folder 882)
    - Beckett, James D., et al., 1916 (Box 47, Folder 883)
    - Burgh, Emil and Emma vs. H. O. Stone & Company, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 884)
    - Calumet and Chicago Canal and Dock Co. (Box 47, Folder 885)
    - City of Chicago vs. Minna Schmidt, August Witt, William Witt, Jr., and Rose Witt, 1919-20 (Box 47, Folder 886-890)
    - City of Cicero vs. Adel J. Keeler, et al., 1902-04 (Box 47, Folder 891-892)
    - Conklin, H. O., Emma Russell and G. A. Bergtold vs. Emma F. Shaw, 1917-23 (Box 47, Folder 893-895)
      Dispute over land in Logan County, Colorado. George Wilbur invests with Conklin and Bergtold in 1920
    - Corbett, Margaret B. vs. Oscar B. Tallacksen, et al., 1928-30 (Box 48, Folder 896-901)
    - Currens, Ray F., 1926 (Box 48, Folder 902)
    - Deitchman, Hyman, 1923 (Box 48, Folder 903)
    - Dierks, Christian P., 1922-23 (Box 48, Folder 904)
    - Doyle, Emma A., 1920-27 (Box 48, Folder 905)
      See also: Emma A Doyle under Probate, Box 48, folders 815-816
    - Durso, Sam, 1923 (Box 48, Folder 906)
    - Emery, Joseph F., 1915 (Box 48, Folder 907)
    - Engleman, Emma, 1887, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 908)
    - Fadner, George M. and Frederick J. Fadner, 1903-14 (Box 48, Folder 909-910)
    - Hanna, Hugh S., 1920-21 (Box 48, Folder 911)
    - Hapeman, Lydia M., 1928 (Box 48, Folder 912)
    - Kouba, Minnie and George, 1922 (Box 48, Folder 913)
    - Mooney, Lillie B. vs. Charles Valentynowicz, 1912-14 (Box 48, Folder 914)
    - Nemeth, Carl G. vs. Gustave H. Soeffing, et al., 1919-20 (Box 48, Folder 915-916)
    - Ofenloch, Henry and Lydia, 1923 (Box 48, Folder 917)
    - Parker, Martha C. H., 1922 (Box 48, Folder 918)
    - Ready and Callaghan Coal Company vs. O. M. Powers, 1916 (Box 48, Folder 919)
    - Reuter, August and Ernest, 1916-22 (Box 48, Folder 920)
      See also: Ernest Reuter in Other Cases, Box 65, folders 1236-1238
    - Schustek, Daniel and Barbara, 1928-29 (Box 49, Folder 921-922)
    - Sheridan, James W., 1911-25 (Box 49, Folder 923-931)
      Sheridan owned land in Texas and gave Wilbur a fifty year oil and gas lease on 160 acres in Hartley County in 1923
    - Siegel, L. A., 1925 (Box 49, Folder 932)
    - Smedley, Eva A. vs. Edward Cohen, 1920-26 (Box 49, Folder 933)
    - Stone, Carrie L., 1923 (Box 49, Folder 934)
    - Syracuse Wall Paper Company, 1914 (Box 49, Folder 935-936)
    - Tilton, Jennie Nichols, 1916-20 (Box 49, Folder 937-938)
    - Tucker, Isaac vs. Philip Hatowski, et al., 1923-24 (Box 49, Folder 939-940)
    - Wallace, Anna, 1929 (Box 49, Folder 941)
    - Walsh, Bridget, 1920, 1923 (Box 49, Folder 942-943)
    - Young, Nellie M., 1929 (Box 50, Folder 944-945)
  - CASES: STREET IMPROVEMENT FILES
    - Paving in Chicago
      - West Adams Street, 1901-04 (Box 50, Folder 946-948)
      - Alley from York Street to West Polk Street, and between Ashland Boulevard and Marshfield Avenue, 1904 (Box 50, Folder 949)
      - Alleys bounded by Washington Boulevard, Park Avenue, South Kedzie Avenue and South Homan Avenue, 1901 (Box 50, Folder 950)
        See also: Alleys bounded by Washington Boulevard... under Sewers, water mains in Chicago, Box 60, folder 1124
      - Archer Avenue, 1903 (Box 50, Folder 951)
      - Armour Avenue, 1903-04 (Box 50, Folder 952)
      - Ashland Avenue, 1901-23 (Box 50, Folder 953-955)
        Includes North and South Ashland Avenues. Includes cases of City of Chicago vs. Chicago and Western Indiana Railroad Company, et al.; City of Chicago vs. William J. Gilbert, et al.
      - Avers Avenue, 1899 (Box 50, Folder 956)
      - Ballou Street, and others, 1905-06 (Box 50, Folder 957)
      - Bishop Street, 1922 (Box 50, Folder 958)
      - Bryn Mawr Avenue, 1901 (Box 50, Folder 959)
      - "C-E" general, 1901 (Box 50, Folder 960)
        Clybourn Avenue Colorado Avenue Delaware Place South Desplaines Street Evanston Avenue
      - California Avenue, 1901 (Box 50, Folder 961)
      - Carpenter Street, 1901 (Box 50, Folder 962)
        Includes South Carpenter Street
      - Center Avenue, 1902 (Box 50, Folder 963)
      - Central Park Avenue, 1901-06 (Box 50, Folder 964)
        Includes both North and South Central Park Avenues
      - South Chicago Avenue, 1904 (Box 50, Folder 965)
      - North Clark Street, 1898-1901 (Box 50, Folder 966)
      - Clinton Street, 1901-03 (Box 50, Folder 967)
      - Columbia Avenue, 1904 (Box 50, Folder 968)
      - Diversey Street, 1897-1905 (Box 51, Folder 969-980)
        Includes cases Elizabeth Boyd, et al. vs. The City of Chicago; Josiah Cratty, et al. vs. The City of Chicago
      - Douglas Boulevard, 1894-1906 (Box 52, Folder 981-995)
        Includes cases John D. Murphy, et al. vs. West Chicago Park Commissioners; The People ex rel., West Chicago Park Commissioners vs. John J. Hanberg, County Treasurer
      - Elizabeth Street, 1904 (Box 52, Folder 996)
      - Flournoy Street, 1901-02 (Box 52, Folder 997)
      - Francisco Street, 1904-05 (Box 53, Folder 998-999)
      - Fulton Street, 1899-1901 (Box 53, Folder 1000)
      - Green Street, 1901-04 (Box 53, Folder 1001)
      - "H-L" general, 1899-1901 (Box 53, Folder 1002)